Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/alaa-ayman-852b94217 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Team work leader Management projects Google Analysis

Languages

Arbic (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Digital Marketing Basics in 40 Hours Edrak

Alaa Ayman

seo specialist

المنصورة

Summary

An SEO Expert with over 4 years of experience working on hundreds of projects from A to Z, in different niches.

I've worked in different countries, around The Middle East and in the Gulf area, where I was responsible for managing different teams of programmers, designers, CRO specialists, and marketing teams.

I follow the latest updates in the field daily, and I'm always developing new strategies to improve website ranking.

To achieve the best results, I use different tools like Pagespeed, GTmetrix, Analytics, Keyword Planner, Search Console, Google Trends, Seo-spider, Ahrefs, Semrush, Moz, Google Merchant Center, Google My Business.

I work on platforms like Laravel, Zid, Salla, Wordpress, Shopify, Opencart, Expancart, Personal Programming, Magento, and other free platforms.

My tasks are:

Perform comprehensive SEO checks, assess the current state of the site, identify problems, weaknesses, and strengths, and create the final SEO plan.

Create a detailed keyword research profile, find out the search volume and competitiveness of all relevant keywords or phrases to create a priority plan to target the least competitive keyword phrases. Conduct a comprehensive competitive analysis to help improve keyword targeting by understanding the factors that SERPs competitors already dominate.

Provide SEO recommendations for updating site code, content and meta tags based on search data and site key performance indicators (KPIs) collected from Google Analytics, Google Search Console, and a variety of tools.

Dealing with external SEO factors, creating high-quality links, creating great viral content for content marketing, and collaborating

with social media executives to handle their tasks in a way that supports your SEO efforts.

Evaluate results with monthly reports on SEO performance, analyze important performance indicators, and compare site results and performance every month.

I also:

Develop myself in various fields such as "Google ads, general marketing, team management, programming basics, networking basics"

Experience

Grand | Community | غران د Seo Expert March 2022 - Present (1 month) العاصمة مدينة الكويت

A new world with Laravel is working to give a new experience in different analyzes and experiences of various problems and successive updates through search engine optimization

Vlinzza Seo Expert March 2022 - Present (1 month)

Flynza works in the field of digital marketing until she reached the magic recipe to jump the profits of our customers to new heights, and sets specific goals, but the results are without ceiling, so I am happy to work on .their site to become the first SEO expert to take responsibility for their site

With the ever-developing WordPress platform

cutestore6 Seo Expert March 2022 - Present (1 month) السعودية

Salla platform is always the best in this type of electronic store. I hope to make more success for that

lunacyshoes

SEO Specialist

February 2022 - Present (2 months)

الرياض السعودية

A new store, one of the largest electronic stores in terms of sales, rises in the sky of the successes of the Shopify platform

مؤسسة أوامر الشبكة لتقنية المعلومات SEO Expert

September 2021 - March 2022 (7 months)

م ص ر

Awamer Alshabaka is a Saudi registered company in the Ministry of Commerce. We have been working in the field of programming for more than 10 years

My tasks in it are:

Perform comprehensive SEO checks, assess the current state of the site, identify problems, weaknesses, and strengths, and create the final SEO plan. Create a detailed keyword research profile, find out the search volume and competitiveness of all relevant keywords or phrases to create a priority plan to target the least competitive keyword phrases.

Conduct a comprehensive competitive analysis to help improve keyword targeting by understanding the factors that SERPs competitors already dominate.

Provide SEO recommendations for updating site code, content and meta tags based on search data and site key performance indicators (KPIs) collected from Google Analytics, Google Search Console, and a variety of tools. Dealing with external SEO factors, creating high-quality links, creating great viral content for content marketing, and collaborating with social media executives to handle their tasks in a way that supports your SEO efforts. Evaluate results with monthly reports on SEO performance, analyze important performance indicators, and compare site results and performance every month.

what I'm doing:

Watching and analyzing customer sites and the factors that need to be improved.

Preparing detailed reports and strategies.

Determine the least expensive but profitable keywords for customer sites.

Improve local search results for the company's website.

Writing effective titles and improving the appearance of the article on the site.

Create an external SEO strategy.

Use crown tags.

Follow the white hat and black hat factors so as not to violate the Google factors.

Develop a tracking strategy and improve the site's tool.

Consult with web designers to improve site performance to boost search results.

see less

04 Academy- أكاديمية زيروفور Seo specialist November 2021 - January 2022 (3 months) الإمارات العربية المتحدة

Always striving for success, it's okay to take more time, but the important thing is that you eventually reach the goal that was once impossible

البط - Elbatt 9 months

Search Engine Optimization Manager January 2021 - September 2021 (9 months)

Content Management Specialist January 2021 - May 2021 (5 months) الدقەلىق المنصورة مصر

ماكدونالدز مصر Administration Assistant December 2020 - January 2021 (2 months) الدقەلية المنصورة مصر

العالمية Marketing Director November 2020 - December 2020 (2 months) الدقولية المنصورة مصر

مجموعة الشوا التجارية Sales Manager February 2020 - May 2020 (4 months) الدقولية المنصورة مصر كانون Customer Service Manager February 2019 - April 2019 (3 months)

الدقهلية المنصورة مصر

العالمية جروب secretariat December 2018 - January 2019 (2 months) الدقەلية المنصورة مصر

الأصدقاء كار Owner August 2015 - September 2018 (3 years 2 months) الدقهلية المنصورة مصر

first step Managing Director October 2017 - July 2018 (10 months) الدقەلية المنصورة مصر

Education

جامعة الدلتا للعلوم والتكنولوجيا درجة البكالوريوس , هندسة الحاسب الآلي (September 2017 - June 2020)